In case you was too cheap to purchase our last game,
let me tell ya a bit about what happened.
It was all about this Abe guy,
that worked in this dumb meat factory, called RuptureFarms.
The place was ran by Glukkons
and the were on the verge of running out of Business.
They had already chopped up all the wild creatures
so now they no choice, but to chop up Abe and his buddies too.
Oh no, no.
We gave Abe the ability to talk!
So he could do the right thing and rescue his pals.
Hello! Hello! Follow me! Ok!
But some people didn't care about doing the right thing...
They thought it was more fun to get them all shot!
Or ground up!
Or crushed!
Or even beaten!
Needless to say,
this pissed some folks off.
And they didn't lift a finger to help Abe in the end.
But if you was halfway decent about it,
and tried your best to save Abe's buddies.
The end would have been much better for Abe.
And if you'd like to see it...
You should dish out some cash and go buy this stinking game!
And we gotta eat too you know.