We're screwed! Pants! I need some pants! Pants!
It's not fair!
We had twice ze flavour.
[Screams of agony.]
I got out of there just in time;
and I got the usual reception.
Abe! It's Abe! It's Abe! It's Abey!
It's that Abe guy! It's that Abe guy!
Abe's ok and he's here to stay!
The Mudokons were slowly coming together;
and they were using their skills to build something new.
Ah!
D'oww!
That gotta hurt!
[Screams of pain.]
You'll be fine. It'll all work out.
See? It's all feeling better already.
Hello. My name is Alf.
Hi Alf!
I had my first brew
while I was with Abe in the desert.
Wow.
They were taking things one step at a time.
Can I share now?
No, just shut up!
All was going well.
But we knew there had to be more of us out there.
We're screwed...
And we were gonna find 'em!
We interrupt this program to bring you this special news bulletin.
Rumor Kontrol reports that Abe,
the terrorist mastermind behind the destruction of RuptureFarms,
is also behind the SoulStorm Brewery atrocity.
I hate that guy!
Stay tuned for more on this story as it develops.
This message brought to you by:
And don't even think about runnin' it on your measly 32-bit system!