This is Necrum.
Long ago the Mudokons brought their dead here.
That was before the Glukkons started stealing our bones.
They used Mudokon slaves to do it.
Blind ones, that couldn't see.
The Glukkons didn't want anyone to know, what they were digging up.
And no one ever did...
Not until the spirits of those bones paid me a visit.
It's Abe!
That's me.
My name is Abe.
I had just returned from saving 99 Mudokons
from RuptureFarms.
That's when they came to see me.
Abe!
You're the savior of the Mudokons.
So you gotta help us.
The Glukkons are digging up our bones.
You gotta come to Necrum, Abe.
Quickly!
We had to do something,
so me and some others left to search for Necrum.
Our journey started well,
we were kind of excited.
Abe, you're just the greatest!
O-Okay.
But by lunchtime,
we were getting pretty tired.
Come on!
Okay.
How much longer?
By dinner it was unbearable.
It's 'cause of you we're in this mess.
This bites.
Can I go home?
What's that?!
I don't know.
Something big!
Where's that coming from?
Hey, look at that.
It's a bone.
I think we're close.
Let's go!
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go.