Oi! Take the [SOMETHING], something to drink!
Don't drink that!
Why not?
Cuz, uh... If brew is made by Glukkons,
it's probably bad for you.
What a wuss!
I hear ya.
Look Abe,
we came all this way, just to help you.
Well but-
It's not unreasonable, that we are just a little bit thirsty.
Now is it?
Yeah, but-
In case you didn't notice, we just walked across a desert.
So back off, Stich-Lips.
But... D'ohhh!
I tried to stop them.
But they drank the brew anyway.
Lot's of it...
Then they got all sick looking.
But they still wanted more!
That's when I figured this whole thing out.
Brew was made from our bones!
This is bad, what do I do now?
What do you do? How about leading us outta here?
Uh, ok. Follow me!
Okay...
But!
[Screaming]
Oops, I forgot he was blind!
Help the rescue the rest of them!
I can't believe it!
That's him, it's that Abe guy!
Promotion, here I come!
Freeze!