This is Rupture Farms.
They say it's the biggest meat processing plant on Oddworld.
I used to work here.
Well... I was really a slave.
...like all the others.
That's me.
My name is Abe.
I was employee of the year.
...now I'm dead meat.
I crossed the meanest boss in the world...
...Mullock the glukkon.
My whole life changed in just one day.
I was working late one night...
at RuptureFarms.
We used to make Meech Munchies.
Until the Meeches were through.
We still made Paramite Pies.
And we made some good Scrab Cakes too.
I thought I had a good job.
But that was before I knew...
How we'd make New 'n' Tasty...
I was still to find.
The truth, it turned out.
Now that would blow my mind...
The glukkons were scared
'cause profits were grim.
Slig: There they are!
Glukkon: Hey, y'guys, you see that?
Paramites and Scrabs had been turning out thin.
Mullock: As you can see, things are going down
Glukkon: What you gonna do about it, huh?
Molluck: Watch.
But Molluck was cool...
Molluck: Show 'em.
Slig: Allright, boss.
He had a plan...
Glukkon: But how?
This new kind of meat...
IT WAS US!
Mullock: We'll chop 'em up.
I just had to escape...
I just had to be free...
and I didn't even know...
I had a destiny.
So...
Get me outta' here!